Guide to the University of Utah football video collection 1948-1999
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Coach's films: games, 1993-1998 (Box 88)
  - Utah vs. SMU, 1997; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2099)
  - Utah vs. TCU, 1997; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2100)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2101)
  - Utah vs. Hawaii, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2102)
  - Utah vs. BYU, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2103)
  - Utah vs. SDSU, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2104)
  - Utah vs. Fresno State, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2105)
  - Utah vs. Louisville, 1998; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2106)